welcome friends my name is Karan
and welcome to this YouTube channel of Trade Solution
as you all
know that today was the budget day and today the
budget was presented by the Finance Minister and
as the Finance Minister had
said that this time's budget is going to be a
historic budget and
you people would have never seen such a budget and it happened just like that this
budget which was
presented by the Finance Minister, it really
proved to be a historic budget as
we had never seen before and due to
which we have seen
a very stormy boom in the market today if we
talk about the hot soil then the
effort that has been made is
around the level of 14200 81, Nifty has jumped by about
646 points, if we look at it in percentage then the
soil has also gained by about 4.74 percent
that if we talk about 50 stocks of Nifty-50 then out of 50
stocks of Nifty-50,
45  Stocks have closed with gains and five
stocks have closed with losses. Now
in today's budget,
a very big announcement has been made by the Finance Minister regarding a chapter,
about which we
will discuss with you in this video today. So
let's start, if we talk about that
chapter regarding which a very big
announcement has been made, then it is the
insurance sector. In this budget of yours,
a big announcement has been made by the Finance Minister regarding the insurance sector
and what is there in it, that is, the
everyday limit of the insurance sector,
now everyday limit means foreign
direct investment limit, the
FD limit of the insurance sector, which used to be 59% earlier, has been
increased to 4974%, so
what will happen with this is that the
insurance sector will benefit from this, that if the foreign
companies, the foreign companies,
want to invest money in the insurance sector in India, then now they can
invest up to 50% (4%) in comparison to earlier, so that the
insurance sector  The
interest of foreign companies in the
insurance sector will increase further, due to which
in the training session of ART, we also got to see
a very good action in the companies of the insurance sector.
If we talk about the
companies of the insurance sector, then there are
six companies found in the insurance sector,
first HDFC Life, second SBI
Life, third ICICI Prudential, fourth
ICICI Lombard, fifth New India
Assurance and sixth General Insurance
Corporation and now we will discuss these six companies one by one
in detail, so
let's start, now let's
first talk about HDFC Life,
as you all are seeing, the
details of HDFC Life have opened in front of us
and if we talk about its today's price, then it will be
seen at 698 25 paise, approximately Rs 20, 30 paise
higher, if we look at the percentage, then
it has been confirmed with a rise of about three percent.
If we talk about Prevents, then it will be seen at 677,
95 paise higher, it opens at
678, Rs 30  But yes it makes
713 rupees for 30 rupees and inside it we
get to see that 668 rupees will be deducted. Now we will
talk about SBI Life's
loot.
So as you can see,
today's details of SBI Life will open in front of us
and if we talk about its today's attempt, then
you will see ₹70 at
about 1255 paise above. If we
look at the percentage, then it has been confirmed with a rise of about 1.45 percent.
If we talk about tips, then
we will see 864 broken 45 paise above. It is
not there, it is
above 875. Yes it makes 897 rupees and
inside it we get to see 852
rupees for five paise. Now let's talk about
ICICI Prudential's
show more
loot. So as you can see, the
details of ICICI Prudential have been done in front of us
and if we
talk about its today's attempt, then it will give us 427 rupees for 50 rupees.  But it will be
seen at about six and a half above. If we
look at the percentage above, then
it has been confirmed with a rise of about 1.35 percent. If we
talk about the press, then it will be
seen at Rs.481, there it is
₹400.35 fixed above, yes it makes ₹
500.45 from above and inside it we get to see
₹400.70 paise. Now let's talk about
ICICI Lombard's
loot
loot. So as you guys are seeing, the
details of ICICI Lombard have opened in front of us
and if we talk about it today, then we will
see it at Rs.1376.10 paise, about 60
percent clear. If we look at the percentage above, then it has been
confirmed with a rise of about 4.61 percent. If we talk about the tips, then it will be
seen at Rs.1315.50, there it is at
Rs.1326.10, yes
it makes  It is 1381, above new paise tax and
inside it we get to see 1295,
so let's now talk about New India
Assurance, so
as you can see, the
details of New India Assurance have
opened in front of us and if we talk about its today's
rule, then 139 will be
seen above it, almost 12 paise above it
and if we look at the percentage, then it has been confirmed
with a very explosive rise of about 9.45 percent,
if I do it after this, then
we will see 127 on it,
it opens above 128 rupees,
yes it makes 142, that is 40% and
inside it we get to see 85 paise on 127,
so let's now talk about the last
General Insurance Corporation, so
as you can see, the details
of General Insurance Corporation have
opened in front of us and if we
talk about its confirmation, then 138 will be
seen on it, approximately Rs 6.10 paise.  If we
look at the percentage above, there
is a disclosure with a rise of about 4.62 percent. If we
talk about the previous, then we will
see the new price at 131. It opens at
13250. Hi, it makes 144
rupees and here we see 13245 inside it. So
these are some details in front of us about the
big announcement made regarding the insurance sector in today's budget. So
with this I
complete this video. Pause this video.
SIM is not destroyed.
Before taking any kind of action, do consult your advisor
and do take your own direction.
If you liked the video,
then do not forget to like and share this video
and do subscribe to our channel.
Thank you.